

Muhammad Javed Shahazad MEAN Stack developer | Ionic | Angular | Node is

+92.307.4557323

Grain Market, Nankana Sahib, Pakistan

Summary

MEAN-Stack Ionic/Angular Developer with 4+ years of proven experience at UssCyber, Appolek, Oxygen Soft, and Fiverr in helping companies create and maintain a better code base for reusability. Always follow and find the best way for problem-solving. Capable of continuous learning from senior developers. Passionate about learning and development with a desire to apply skills on a larger development team. Always Eager to tackle more complex problems and continue to find ways to maximize user efficiency. Always tried my best to deliver the stuff before the deadline and make sure everything is implemented according to the expectations.

Skills

- Android Development
- Firebase
- IONIC Angular Framework
- Laravel Framework
- MySQL
- PHP

- Android Studio
- Google Maps Knowledge
- iOS Development
- Mobile Phone App Development
- Node Js
- Postgres Databases

- Angular Framework
- HTML CSS bootstrap
- JavaScript
- MongoDB
- OOP
- Xcode

Experience

MEAN Stack developer | Ionic | Angular | Node js

UssCyber Inc, Miami, Florida, USA

Working as a MEAN Stack developer including IONIC Angular Framework.

My roles are as follows

- Building dynamic and adaptable Web/Mobile applications.
- Design and develop REST FULL APIS in Node js.
- Integrating APIS in Ionic Angular apps.
- Design and Develop UI in Ionic Angular Framework.
- Delivering comprehensive front-end software.
- Publish and maintain apps in app stores like Apple and Play Store.
- Developing front-end applications and asset infrastructure.
- Maintain and push code in GitHub.

Full-Stack developer | Ionic | Angular | NodeJs | Firebase | Php | Laravel

Fiverr, Lahore, Pakistan

Jan 2019 - Present

Jan 2023 - Present

I am working as a Full-stack Ionic/Angular and Node Js developer as a freelancer part-time.

My services are as follows:

- Develop and Design apps in Ionic Angular Framework
- Write Rest full Apis in Node js
- · Firebase database as backend
- Publishing apps in the App store and Play Store
- Develop and implement logic in the Php language

Here is my Profile Link: https://www.fiverr.com/javedshahazad?public_mode=true

Full-Stack Ionic/Angular Developer

Appolek Inc, Goteborg, Sweden

Feb 2020 - Mar 2021

I worked there as a Full-Stack Ionic/Angular Developer.

My responsibilities are as follows

- Write and Design Resfull Apis in Php with MySql
- Design responsive UI in Ionic Angular.
- Integrate Apis and logic implementation in Ionic Angular Framework.
- Write useful and clean code, Clean commits to GitHub.
- Maintain and publish apps in Google Play Store and Apple Store.

Full-Stack Php Laravel Developer

oxygensoft.org, Lahore, Pakistan

Jun 2019 - Feb 2020

I worked there as a Full-Stack PHP Laravel developer.

My roles are as follows:

- Design and Develop responsive UI in Laravel.
- Implement logic and write code in PHP Laravel with Mysql Database.
- Clean pushes to GitHub.
- Maintain multiple projects in Php.

Education

Government College University Faisalabad

Bachelors in Science 2020

Computer Science

CGPA: 3.1/4

BISE Lahore

Intermediate/A-Level 2016

lcs

Percentage: 75%

BISE Lahore

Matriculation/O-Level 2014

Arts

Percentage: 80%

Projects

XLiquidus

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.usscyber.xliquiduss.app

About Project:

XLiquidus is an intuitive platform for crypto investors of all levels looking to buy and liquidate cryptocurrencies. XLiquidus is the liquidation app of choice from WSCE Token and Exchange holders.

My Roles:

- Design and develop REST FULL APIS in Node is.
- Integrating APIS in Ionic Angular apps.

- Design and Develop UI in Ionic Angular Framework.
- Delivering comprehensive front-end software.

CitiMovers

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.waldsolutions.citimovers About Project:

The smart way to move at low costs. It's developed in the IONIC Angular framework with the Firebase backend. It helps users to move from one place to another place with their assets.

- Design responsive UI in Ionic Angular
- Implement and manage data in Firebase
- Firebase database as backend
- Publish and maintain the app in the Google Play store and App Store

Nightscard: Nightlife & Offers

https://play.google.com/store/apps/details?id=com.nightscard.cla

Nightscard helps you unlock the best nightlife experiences in your city. Using Nightscard means you're part of the ultimate members club, helping you explore and unlock the best nightlife your city has to offer. Whatever you want from your night, we make it easy for you to find the best spots it your city. What's more, we're partnering with numerous venues to offer you amazing discounts and offers. So whether you've just been paid, or your payday has come and gone already, you can be sure that you never miss out when you use Nightscard.

Tecca Ionic angular framework Hybrid app

https://cheery-zuccutto-cdcbba.netlify.app/login

Tecca app is a hybrid app to manage Teacher and student activity. It helps teachers and students to assign and submit activities more easily and digitalized way. A teacher can assign activities to their students. The students can check and complete the activity and submit it to the teacher for review. The teacher can review the activity and assign the next one.

Duchnne Hybrid App

Duchenne app for managing the staff of an office.

I developed this app for my Fiverr client. He is from Germany.

Carwash Hybrid mobile App

The Carwash app is developed in the Ionic angular framework with a PHP backend. It helps the carwash shop owner to increase their business with an online booking system. The user can select the service, pick a time and go to the car wash shop to wash their car. In this way, they can save too much time and go to the car wash shop when they feel free.

Restaurant Management

Hotel management in PHP Laravel web app. It helps restaurant owners to increase their business and productivity. The owner can add the items that have in their hotel and many more actions.

The users can select the items, book an order or go to the hotel and book a table. They can order items and have much more fun.

刄	Languages
---	-----------

English Urdu Expert Expert